(Howard:)...I'll see you around.
(Howard:)See you.
(Raj:)No, wait.
(Raj:)Take her number.
I don't want the temptation.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Raj:)I must be strong so I don't stray from
my true purpose: The study of the universe.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Howard:)Thanks for ruining lobster for me.
(Raj:)Wait! Give me the number!
(Raj:)Give me the number! Give me the number!
(Leonard:)So, Amy, what's going on
with your addiction study?
(Amy:)Sadly I'm no longer associated
with that project.
- Why? What happened?
- Typical bureaucratic nonsense.
(Amy:)You can get animals addicted to a harmful
substance, you can dissect their brains...
...but you throw their own feces back at them
and suddenly you're unprofessional.